

Do Nguyen Vuong

General Director at Trend Motor Vietnam (Volkswagen Vietnam)

Connect

♠ Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month



Connect

△ Message

• • •

Do Nguyen Vuong · 3rd

General Director at Trend Motor Vietnam (Volkswagen Vietnam)

Vietnam · 500+ connections · Contact info

Trend Motor Vietnam (Volkswagen Vietnam)

Maastricht School of Management

About

Experienced Group Managing Director with a demonstrated history of working in the automotive industry. Skilled in Negotiation, Business Planning, Operations Management, Coaching, and Retail. Strong sales professional with a MBA focused in General Strategic and Management from Maastricht School of Management.

Activity

Posts Do Nguyen created, shared, or commented on in the last 90 days are displayed here.

See all activity

Experience

General Director

Trend Motor Vietnam (Volkswagen Vietnam)
Oct 2019 – Present
· 1 yr 7 mos

Managing Director

Dai A Importer (Jaguar Land Rover VN)
Dec 2018 – Feb 2020
· 1 yr 3 mos

Managing Director - Automotive Group

New City Group Sep 2018 – Oct 2019 · 1 yr 2 mos

Importers of Jaguar Land Rover, Maserati, Volkswagen and Retailers of Ford, Hyundai

Master Coach



Dealer Principal

Vietnamstar Mercedes-Benz Sep 2014 – May 2018 · 3 yrs 9 mos HCM cum Nha Trang Autohaus

Show 5 more experiences 🐱

Education

Maastricht School of Management MBA, General Strategic and Management 2007 – 2009 Dai hoc Mo' Bán Công Tp. Hô Chí Minh BS, Business Administration 1994 – 1996

University of Technology

BS, Automotive 1987 – 1992

Skills & endorsements

Negotiation . 21



Endorsed by Kevin Nguyen, who is highly skilled at this



Endorsed by 3 of Do Nguyen's colleagues at Ford Motor Company

Management . 12



Endorsed by 3 of Do Nguyen's colleagues at Ford Motor Company

Retail . 12



Endorsed by 2 of Do Nguyen's colleagues at Ford Motor Company

Industry Knowledge

Business Strategy \cdot 12

Business Planning . 12

Sales Management . q **Business Development** . 7 New Business Development . 5 **Customer Satisfaction** . 5 **Operations Management** . 4 Marketing . 3 **Dealer Management** Interpersonal Skills **Leadership Development** . 8 Coaching . 8 **Team Building** . 6 Leadership . 5 **Executive Coaching** . 4 **Customer Service** . 4 Show less ^ Recommendations

Received (0) Given (1)

Kamarul Zaman

Retired Senior Management - Retail & Distribution
January 4, 2019, Do Nguyen was Kamarul's mentor

I was very lucky to work with Kamarul over a number of years when we implemented Quality Care program for Ford dealers in Vietnam. Actually I have learned a lot from him. He is very professional, enthusiastic and supportive.

Interests

General Motors

2,607,513 followers



McKinsey & Company







AN ^{39,513} members

Google

21,135,007 followers



Jack Welch in





Chief Executive Officer at Ford Motor Company 23,996 followers



People also viewed



Andreas Klingler •3rd

General Director Porsche Vietnam

Connect



Genet Laurent •3rd

General Director Audi Vietnam and Chairman Audi Cambodia, CFAO Country Director

Connect



Tran Hoang Hai •3rd

General Manager at Toyota Motor Vietnam

Connect



Dr. Frauke Schmitz-Bauerdick •3rd

Director Vietnam at Germany Trade & Invest

Connect



Tran Nam •3rd

Deputy General Manager at Isuzu Vietnam Company

Connect

Show more Show more

People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Connect



Nhi Duong

Stuc	lent at	Ton I	Duc T	hand	Unive	rcity
Stuc	ieni ai	1011	Duc i	Hally	OHIVE	SISILY

Connect

∨Show more



Add new skills with these courses



128,152 viewers



Soft Skills for Sales Professionals

173,787 viewers



Building and Managing a High-Performing Sales Team

20,367 viewers

Show more on LinkedIn Learning

Linked in

About

Accessibility

Talent Solutions

Community Guidelines

Careers	
Marketing Solutions	
Privacy & Terms ❤	
Ad Choices	
Advertising	
Sales Solutions	
Mobile	
Small Business	
Safety Center	
Questions? Visit our Help Center.	
Manage your account and privacy Go to your Settings.	
Select Language (Arabic)	
inkedIn Corporation © 2021	

